早上好，欢迎打造 8:16 下午
它太棒要回到这里在旧金山欢迎
对每个人都在这里与我们，，以及要让每个人都能加入我们在 web 上。
你知道，我感觉就像我已经标记我成人的生活
与事实想起甚至但 microsoft 开发人员会议
我想在微软的各种平台纪元可能孩子
我的儿子属于 ys
和我的女儿是所有点净，就这样就这样
梦幻般要回来这里和说话给开发商还有一件事
这是关于开发人员会议开发商如此独特
来到这里已经兴奋他们到达的技术
请参阅更多的技术，满足更多的人正在讲话技术
最重要的是他们走开的启发。
他们所看到的他们学会建立更多
冷却器技术开发人员会议的独特性
是我们想要在这里庆祝，接下来的三天
开发人员能够放大技术是我们想要什么
谈论过，当然这次生成会议。
浅谈所有这种技术。
其实还有更多主流的对话。
关于技术的作用。
在我们的社会。
它是正确的时间来对话因为技术更多
主流，它被嵌入在我们的日常生活
它被嵌入在我们我们在我们的经济行业中的公司
和国家比以往任何时候更是如此。
所以，我们有这些。
深层次的问题和问题摆在我们面前。
拉动经济增长每个人的技术吗？
或者经济增长停滞在怨恨吗？
科技花。
是技术赋予人民或它取代我们吗？
技术帮助我们保护我们永恒的价值，如
隐私吗？
或它损害它吗？
这些是正在讨论的问题和他们
我们有广泛的对话，不只是在一个正确的问题
不只是在其中的我们的行业，但作为一个社会的公司。
我 m 的乐观主义者。
我们作为一家公司。
对什么技术可以持乐观态度
做为我们相信技术可以吗
事实上在世界各地推动经济增长？
我相信技术可以增强我们的能力。
我相信技术可以用于保存我们永恒的价值。
然而要使我们对建筑的去的选择
技术。
我们需要做出设计选择。
经济选择和社会选择。
这确保。
我们使用技术的方式帮助了我们构建技术
我们这种乐观情绪作为一个社会进步。
和几个选择嵌入
在我们的使命，赋予每个人编码
和每个组织在星球上实现更多。
想让我们这样的人。
可以做的事情、 把事情做好吗？
这是我们广阔的平台方法。
并且，当我们想到开车成功吗？
和，赋予人民和企业通过数字
技术。
我们必须开始与所有的您作为开发人员，我们有
要赋予你力量与技术，但更重要的是我们必须
创建这个机会让你能够表达你
创造力。
这可以改变世界，在这个开发人员大会，是我们想谈什么
关于平台，
你去上班，真的。
我打算帮你改变世界吗？
我们生活在我们已经讨论了移动第一云第一次世界
过很多次之前但它总是很好回去要确保。
我们植根于我们的移动云先的意思。
对于我们移动首先不是任何单个设备的流动性
它是人类经验的流动跨所有设备
那计算在我们的生活。
云计算不是一个单一的目的地。
云计算是一种新形式的计算。
事实上使，那流动性经验跨我们的设备
它需要将这些经验注入智力，因为它有
理智战胜了大量的数据使用的分布式计算能力
是什么是丰富移动第一云第一个世界，我们正在建设的织物。
而且，我们正在建立三个相互联系的平台。
到明天
你想要听到从袭击了我们的智能云和 azure 三。
斯科特的要广泛谈
如何为所有新的应用程序模式入手
物联网 ttwo 移动设备访问 web，机器学习如何
您可以使用数据和基础设施建造这些
应用程序更重要的他要谈一谈如何。
建设
更多的 azure 使您有机会能达到超过 5
那些已经在蔚蓝的 active directory 中的万业务。
齐鲁要明天谈机会与办公室
五三六。
我们开放给办公室三六五与以往不同的你
应用程序数据到办公室三六五连接器。
外接程序可以发现内
很自然地深受广大用户的办公室办公，ui 脚手架。
那是办公室的个点亿用户
最终将能够得到对所有应用程序的访问，因为他们得到
我们也要以丰富的 ui 脚手架内置
下面是人及其关系的办公室的语义信息
这会安排他们的文件和所有其他的工件
并将它作为微软图公开，以便您可以使用它
您可以扩展您的应用程序的一部分
所以奶酪想要谈论那富有的世界是什么样子。
而且，今天早上。
樱桃和我会谈论更多的个人计算。
Windows 十已关闭。
到一个惊人的开始。
它是增长最快的 windows 版本中这两个消费者和
企业。
我们对设备的巨大创新。
事实上它是新的 windows 设备类别是否物联网
获取创建 t 或全息透镜。
今天早上你会听到从特里团队
关于所有与 windows 进展如何
无论是触摸，我们正在自然的用户界面。
油墨的声音。
或甚至图像识别。
所以，你可以使用它们来构建新的应用程序类别。
我们也想要谈一谈如何。
在游戏和消费应用程序中，我们要开放
pc 和领事申请开发人员的新机遇。
我们也要谈谈 windows 如何是你的极限
你可以在那里做你所有的应用程序开发的开发框
为 windows 和超越 windows pc 上那儿。
我们还想谈谈我们新的新兴平台。
在那里它非常早期的阶段，这实际上是插入节吗？
我们的所有三个目标的记得它对话作为一个平台。
它是一个简单的概念，但它是非常强大的影响
是以我们的人类语言。
它应更普遍适用于所有我们计算。
这意味着我们需要注入我们的电脑和
计算智力、 智力关于我们和我们的上下文。
并通过这样做，我们认为。
这可以有问深刻影响作为以前的平台转移
了无论是 gui 无论是 web
是触摸的手机上。
因此，我们有广泛谈论的这个新的平台旅程开始，但
我们想要开始与 windows 十和什么机会
代表所有的你，让我在舞台上请欢迎，但特里迈尔森的做谢谢你吗？
萨摩亚。
所以，回到这里很兴奋和
充满了你们我的意思是它真的是这样伟大的时间是
windows 开发人员，今天它要变得更好。
萨提亚与 windows 共享我们的抱负是使
计算多个个人和改变我们所有人与交互的方式。
得益于技术使我们更多的互动与设备
凭直觉
使用自然语言的对话。
我们进化机械键盘和鼠标。
会谈。
内外，利用
更多人类的功能，如我们的声音
因此我们的脸手势指纹。
把业务拓展到今天的电脑和手机。
使计算进我们的世界。
与跨设备让自己沉浸在游戏的全息图。
Windows 十是我们的家园
这种演变使我们做得更有效率，使我们能有更多的乐趣。
Windows 网球已出八个月。
是已被积极使用超过 2 亿 7000 万人？
而客户却比以往任何时候都更多参与
在 windows 上十支出超过 750 亿小时。
和，他们发射了超过我们硬件合作伙伴
五百年新设备为 windows 设计与大晒黑设备
屏幕较小的屏幕没有屏幕和一切在这两者之间。
又或者感动这种反应在全球各地，？
在三藩市，在这里就在这里。
现在。
这并不仅仅是这一势头可以 windows 网球后的
最快通过的任何版本的 windows 曾经和
不只是消费者也是其企业客户
考虑只是美国国防部的百万设备窗体
万设备将升级到 windows 往往只是这一年？
所以，整个 windows 团队代表们高兴地欢迎所有这些
客户到 windows 十在那里他们有一个全新的 pc 机
五岁的 pc。
或全新 mac 加入我们，欢迎在 windows 上十。
现在每一天我们正在努力为更好地制作 windows 十
取悦我们世界各地的用户。
和今天
非常高兴与你们分享我们已经工作在下一波的创新
微软对 windows 十周年更新吗？
今年夏天来自由所有的 windows 十个客户。
萨摩亚。
你 windows 内部人士有多少？
一个 windows 业内人士在那里。
所以，令人敬畏我从秃头团队的意思是这件事情再一次你们两个
帮助塑造一切我们做
微软给我们的反馈每天对每个像素的每盎司
我们可以挤压性能，当然今天你可以去下载最新信息
生成和给我们的反馈和一切我们今天要谈与此
周年纪念更新更多的个人计算真正会来更多的生活。
那窗户你好。
今天的你
可以更安全、 方便地登录到您的设备比以往任何时候。
但是，现在要能够使用这此周年更新安全和
简单的生物特征认证与您的应用程序或甚至更好
与微软边现在是第一个也是只到浏览器
支持此安全和易于生物身份验证对所有支持的网站。
周年纪念更新将引入的所有新 windows 油墨体验我们的目标是
请与您的设备用无缝和笔和纸一样容易使用泛。
我们设计这个周年更新将现在来到你的 xbox 之一
把所有的 windows 应用程序到您的客厅
允许您打开任何零售 xbox 之一
开发工具包，当然亦是周年更新将到全息透镜
启用所有新方式工作交流学习和玩耍。
和柯塔娜周年更新中
要令人难以置信的新的方式去把事情做好。
所以，请欢迎布莱恩表明你布莱恩 · 罗珀做周年更新演示。
谢谢你特里。
女士们、 先生们，今天早上感觉怎么样人通过这我
是豪华的机会现在如何你的感觉。
与这一周年纪念的令人敬畏现在更新我的男人
泵送我们要完全现代化的 pc，我们要使它更安全
更安全，我们要使它更加个人和生产力和我们要保持
你真正从事与更多的个人计算的想法我想入手
更安全和更安全好作出一些噪音如果你使用 windows 你好今天。
你还记得我们推出这个人的生物特征认证与企业等级保证人们的安全
最个人的事情，可能你的手指你的脸太棒了我们看到爱这个人
艺术家来应用人购买使用这个 dropbox 集成 windows 商店里的东西
今天我想谈谈另一部分其非常兴奋，但这就是我们所有正确
那里最大的金融服务提供者，对我们美国军方和他们实际上去
延长使用 microsoft 边缘，因为他们网站你好支持新
最后谱 wthree-c 在边缘中实现这种便捷性和安全性
边缘可以实际上光最多在这里所以，检查出来我们要现在说网站
这是所以现在要滚我的指纹设备容易大量要做
是触摸登录 windows 你好你去了，现在它问我
触摸我的指纹，就像现在这样它记录在它那快，很容易有
安全和可靠。
我们被抽一下。
现在让我们来谈论更多的个人计算和这儿有点生产
对特里提到把墨水前面和中心新经验
好吧我们要帮助您使用 windows 油墨创建酝酿和更好的合作
好的应用程序和我们为什么为什么你要把墨水前面和中心因为这布莱恩
允许你仍然是用笔和纸制造一些噪音，如果你仍然写下所有的时间用笔和纸的东西吗？
我们为什么要做做信贷快速很容易的就有它是媒体它
不需要安装但然后有时失去了那张纸，和你知道，你
我们在哪里了，所以我们的 windows 油墨的目标是真正结合起来的人
自然和笔和纸的速度 power pc 这四个零件这第一，我们要去
把这笔前面和中心，所以要用它做什么你知道，第二我们要确保我们解决
人伸手去拿笔和纸最好几个的任务三个我要去告诉你如何 windows 油墨实际上是
更深层次的平台，使整个 windows 更快和更流畅的墨水流
好吧让我们开始与第一张放笔前面和中心的经验好，就我的钢笔的时候我
超级激动，但我总是不知道该怎么办，是哪个应用程序使用，所以我们正在解决的
我要推进这笔按钮检查这一点这是油墨工作区
油墨在这里的所有东西，这些都是人们做我要跳入水中，在第二个，但大部分的三个任务
看看这个我最近使用的笔应用程序我可以回到中和做我也下了做的事这里提示和技巧
用户要知道该怎么办我们要你走过那另一件事，我想要叫你的人这一权利在这里这支笔
建议应用程序，这是在哪里如果碰了这我要去一个地方
我们专门的商店，只是令人惊异的应用程序支持钢笔节我们所以我们要去
光为乡亲要知道该怎么办的笔，我们把它放右前与中心是你想的吗？
根据入门正确。
我们最完成的任务呢
第一我们记下事情要记住让一些噪音如果你在你的生活中使用粘滞便笺吗？
我没事不惊讶三 m
卖五十亿元粘注意到一年吧所以他们在我们的 windows san 上
800 万的粘滞便笺和 300 万每日活跃用户的每月活跃用户所以当然
我们会做的更好我认为它是我粘滞便笺就在这里看看这个，在这里我有一些东西
确保我表明你们到目前为止所做的好，但是看看这个我要
新记在这里我妈妈总是担心时我做演示，因为我，你知道，
她说她将它混合了较早时候在拉丁人的西班牙式布莱恩我担心这一演示
好的你感觉在此之后我总是数常见妈妈我多么想确保
明天打电话给妈妈，但看我写的时候，会发生什么
明天好吧看看多么容易各光滑这种墨水流动的第一，但
看看什么发生了接下来我写明天这个词，因为我们结合我们的笔和电脑你看到它变成蓝色
那是因为我们是足够聪明，知道那是手写，知道那是一天所以如果碰到岩石我温馨
在提醒柯塔娜是很容易能够上来了，实际上这一提醒给我安排好和
超越只设置提醒柯塔娜 bing 是整合将能够识别的地方了
欧洲地图这要很聪明，这些粘滞便笺是天才，你们是怎么想的。
我们为什么别的写下来有时，你从头开始出主意的事情
它是容易视觉沟通多少次
移动的家具你扯下一张纸你开始记上
它你开发者知道你助跑到白色板写一堆东西，然后在结束了像全白色让我拍照
当时的白板和稍后尝试破译那些东西到底是这很有道理
好了我们想要确保你有办法做到这一点，这就是为什么还有一本速写本现在这么检查了这
出速写本已经写了一些东西在这里为你和你要看看是我
当然写 windows 爱油墨我可以得到所有你会点点头那该多好它
是平滑黄油所以查阅这虽然所以我们把墨水前面和中心，我要去打
你在这里的一些统计数据与我们做一个小调查发现那七十二 %
人还有用笔和纸或各种书写工具很多
少七十二 %实际上更多的用户
比那没事疯狂现在的那七个中将一天每一小时
现在三十二 %实际使用它为更多的七十二 %
比三个小时一天所以有很多人都正确使用钢笔现在检查
那它是怎么被快速很容易就被立即我那里我可以说明一个想法你因为我想要呼喊，因为我
有我们的 pc 能像有一把尺子，也许这些线条不是作为冷却我一个很酷
他们很容易被 outlook 能够进来和旋转这我能进来并得到我
线超直能和这所有你喜欢它吗你
滞后这很酷，当然最后一件事这是底部如果我不做它
赎罪成员回小学的首先学习的是，每当你有一颗心你
穿心一箭，这样做是好的现在因为这是
pc 是 app 那个人是我写的那颗心心里兴奋
所以我不会失去这个白板，因为我有可能使人
电力-电脑，你知道，什么看起来有这为后来我去前方和推
到-你，所以这种方式是有它你还记得我们爱油墨你们是怎么想的？
当然我们不想要的方式，所以实际上去和锁定我的电脑现在查阅这
很多得到的那整个油墨工作区是可用上面锁我可以回去自己在做什么
时的摇滚你抓住您的设备与大规模按钮你准备去的人
好吧。
现在超越这个很酷的东西墨是一个平台，其实如此
现在真的展示如何此扩展的大墨经验中的一些事情吗
办公室的地图应用程序，我们有，然后还在 adobe 这么检查了这出
开始与地图有时很难其实向很远的地方作为某人解释某事
一张地图是在哪里看看这个我想让我把我的钢笔，然后打个小 cc 的
正确在这里发生了什么但点缀这点是兴趣的它成为一个点的智能墨水人
作为一个注册的兴趣点要到那边去我某人对你知道，这由水
我让另一个点，现在看看会发生什么，我只是画一条线连接点，并看看会发生什么，这种墨水是
足够聪明，要知道这两个点，要知道那距离和实际上看到发生了什么
好的也就可以看到了我们可以很容易的方向，而是超越，这里是
鼠标的地狱，如果你盆地噪音如果你玩之前，是的这张地图的三维条
如果你有不是你已经要查阅这让我们说我想要去徒步旅行，我发现真的很酷的路线是
现在看看什么会发生这种墨水会很聪明去做再一次足以
干燥机没有注意的二点一英里这我可以让一点地说，这里是我们要去
肉类，然后在这里也可能我们不会停止，并做一些午餐
好，那么最合适的我要去和这里说的这里也许是我们要去
干得很好的图片，所以我做这些自定义知道这些自定义路由他们
可跨所有我 windows 设备但看会发生什么的看看这当我
关闭此油墨是足够聪明，实际上坚持它知道那件事，通过三维
地形映射到它的弹道和观看这当我实际上在转动我写的这个小广告牌
足够聪明，面对我的整个时间作为我们的笔和
pc 聚在一起，你对此的感觉如何？
我要去重温一些童年创伤在这里老师标记红色的东西
论文一贯但检查一下我们都过这出
无论是帮助你的孩子与他们的家庭作业或如果你是一个老师自己但你看，完成
你如何这是在 word 跨向外它消失了也许我不喜欢这整段确定
我们一直有墨字，但看如何文本实际上回流现在还如果你就像
当您突出显示它看起来像这样的东西，是酷看看会发生什么，我没有艺术倾向也许
亚勒应用程序如果你是像好的永远不会写它是你做一个整体
今天也段现在 powerpoint 作为伟大的工作，在对齐的事情
自然但检查垂直水平轴上这个让我告诉你统治者在这里能做什么，
当我用两个手指真的移动这两件事我容易，能够很容易
控制旋转我使用一个旋转锁定
所以我其实可以做的就是这下移这里和这些对象旁边这把尺子对齐
好的这是很容易走到一起，是的可现在当我排队这
检查这一点它真的对我很容易绘制一些人小对角线，使
我令人敬畏的幻灯片看这就是我们的笔和 pc 来在一起好吧现在
超出了办公室，除地图外，我们知道 windows 油墨是一个平台，每个人都和 adobe 拥抱这的对
谈论做某事他们为我们做了看看这个，你现在看到的它什么
来，所以是很假，但这就是被称为法国曲线模具是故意
假货 adobe 不想他们的工具得到艺术家方式好吧但是看看什么会发生同时钢笔和
启用 windows 油墨平台的触动看那位艺术家是如何轻松地使用触摸和
钢笔在一起以便能够时，实际上使这些完美的线条，与我的意思是那是令人敬畏的法语曲线模具鞋
这赋予新经验的科技是不是有罪的方式
其有利的目标在这里你可以看到是延迟的示例的令人惊异
或那里的缺乏更多的 windows 油墨平台墨水完全顺利流出那支笔
我的意思是，你永远不会知道，它是实际设备做，因为这就是我们的目标，你们对此的感觉如何？
女士们、 先生们，只是一个开始你就可以这样没有办法这一切
在舞台上有更多共同作为一种给你看一眼
到我们什么会发生是一个小的嘶嘶声视频采取一看。
那令人敬畏的教学语言。
所有这些经验，布莱恩只是表明是建立在我们普遍的窗户。
我们设计这个平台为所有类型的应用程序从生产力到
游戏。
全息我们设计这个平台为所有类型的设备
手机平板电脑 pc 联网种子大屏幕喜欢表面
集线器和全息透镜或 xbox 和更多。
我们设计这个平台的所有
我们的客户对我们的商业客户的所有需求和对于那些我们的开发
合作伙伴针对消费者，这是一个开放的平台。
三十年 windows 作为欢迎
打开硬件合作伙伴软件开发商合作伙伴生态系统，无论他们身在何处
一轮世界并没有什么变化与通用 windows 平台
通用的 windows 平台汇集所有 windows 历史以及
今天的用户期望从一个现代应用程序平台的一切
微软的无缝和鲁棒的安装卸载和无缝更新。
和我们 2 亿 7000 万的用户的 windows
十他们参观商店超过 5 亿次。
而我们普遍 windows 平台开发者的反应
一些令人难以置信的新应用程序的新开发人员增加月结束
每月 60%增长的只是最后几个月里。
这些开发人员都带来一些令人难以置信的新应用程序到存储区
来很快所以伙伴像 twitter 银行美国星巴克
胡佛迪士尼现蕾 x 雅虎全球摔跤和更多。
Facebook 我们
为 facebook 带来一个新的通用应用程序
instagram 和到商店很快的使者。
如何非常兴奋来分享
facebook 也将他们的 facebook 观众网络应用程序
将 sdk 安装到我们所有的通用 windows 平台开发
zthree 万 facebook 广告商可以达到他们的客户
通过您的应用程序？
现在这不仅仅是。
在处理从大通过的消费空间的势头
我们的商业客户数以千计的组织现在正试用 windows 的使用
他们的组织内的营业的商店
在构建令人难以置信的应用程序，让我们利用看看一个合作伙伴真的走了领先。
波音公司是世界上最大的研究公司，
大多数世界是木板今天我们商业航空公司的航班或
波音畸形三七出来到我们以为那是一个漂亮的数据更丰富
血液机后面七十七个花旗银行产生三十倍之多的数据
麻烦和每一代将会更多。
作为什么波音数字航空的一部分我们开发软件
为航空公司客户提供电子业务效率
袋装的飞行是基本上是从飞行员的工作流
预发布直到大约三或四年前飞飞行员与特里三十
四十英镑的纸或导航那里充路由器喜欢
开发人员显示 windows 十因为平台的灵活性
过渡到它释放
和一些机会，目前我们还没有的内容。
我们未来的业务将会越来越多积累的不同
应用清醒普遍 windows 平台将帮助我们向副驾驶
与实时决策对我们的业务所有关于玷污这数据来下飞机吗
所以，你可以做与普遍的 windows
你只是不能做任何其他平台的平台。
，这是一个开发人员会议，所以我认为它是我们看一些代码的时候了。
请欢迎凯文 · 盖洛。
早上好我很高兴到这里来。
我们知道，每个创新和一大步
windows 只是一样强大的生态系统，集会
周围。
这意味着不只构建投资
但更重要的投资在 windows 客户窗口
为您我们的开发人员并不只构建 windows 应用程序要么
但是否你正在构建你的云服务网站甚至
应用程序相反，我们希望 windows 成为的地方你可以平台
最多产和最成功我们希望 windows 要回家。
对于开发人员来说。
让我们从一些最新的创新，来开始
对普遍的 windows 平台和如何会使开发商获得
推信封有天然的输入和直观的设计。
所以，在这里我有在这里启动它应用成人。
关于本机应用程序现在一件伟大的事
就是能够真正利用我们的 gpu 和令人惊叹的生成和
八分之一点区分您的应用程序的用户体验。
我们已经添加了硬件加速 60 帧每秒
动画效果，这些效果将带来更丰富、 更逼真的设计
创建一种深度分层
和其帮助使您的应用程序，更令人愉快和直观的使用对流动性
我我有无限的应用程序只是几个，我想告诉你这里的第一个和我一样模糊效果
移动我的手指我去这同步的模糊我的手指在完美的和谐
在这里绝对没有毛刺和看起来令人惊叹其分层的其实都是在真正的时间是
没有编造的我们也有能力做基于鼠标的影响
我的鼠标方式就是我得到这些酒吧中你可以看到这张图是任何种类的敌人效果和层
那作为我超过一打到此分层得到很好的感觉的
如何，你知道，实际栏是有实际的图形中所以当我表明
这个夏天设计师可以告诉你他们与这些新的 gpu 是多么兴奋
该 gpu 效果和什么他们都能够去做它的设计现在上
继续前进到我最喜欢的是 windows 油墨类以及如何我们
想要所有的死亡必须能够快速、 轻松地集成墨水
他们与经验，使这支笔来活着为最终用户所以我
会显示你是典型在这里一次会议
你好世界为 windows 油墨要开始用代码的？
我有我的 xaml，所以我建在 xaml 中还有两个控件是这里的第一个
画布的控件，我们介绍了过去一年里这是我在哪里
所有内置了我中风和绘制所有的所有的功能
有趣的新控件的单个控制它是现在已内置于库存控制
sdk 这是墨迹工具栏你布莱恩也使用这有支钢笔
小贴士橡皮和那把尺子，我们表明你所有
不得不做了这样做绑定声明这里从实际工具栏到画布上
知道哪画布行事的是你的全部的 xaml 的两行上
为了做我给你们看我怎么为这两行只是，你知道，
它的真实，所以在这里就可以开始画就在这里在此图表上它
可以突出显示这里指出的东西，我可以也只是弹出我的尺子和
在这里可以移动标尺和你客气也许试图找到有节奏一样好
布莱恩在这和部分地址一些之间它你看到的所有的线
这与 xaml 只是这两行只是那些两行。
它从来没有容易头发富朱向您的应用程序的功能
但当然我们有更多的墨迹 api 主机，所以你可以
建立一些先进的经验表明，布莱恩你这样
这是只是一小来到宇宙的许多特征
平台这个平台中总那里万名新的 api
和现在，结束一天的事情只有成为真正的功能
为开发者们，当你得到你动手所以我 m 兴奋地宣布，今天
我们正在释放视觉工作室更新结束。
周年纪念 sdk 的预览。
给他们一个旋转，让我们知道你的想法。
我想要在中移动下一的步谈 web 开发去年
我们介绍了承载的 web 应用程序，这允许开发人员轻松的带
他们的 web 体验到他们可以利用您现有的 windows 应用商店 web 投资
并在同一时间得到充分利用到本机
功能，如柯塔娜蓝牙油墨和更多这共鸣
我们 web 社区我们看过很多高度额定的 web 应用程序提交到 windows 存储
包括美国快递雅虎邮件 zulily 和更多。
然而，
我们说话要开发 web 开发人员的时候他们仍然挣扎着用
windows 作为其主要的 dev 框，其中许多工作流，
依靠土地开放源代码的命令行工具脚本和框架我们打算去修理
设置，以便 windows 可以是你的家
所以今天我 m 如此兴奋地宣布 bash 外壳吗？
来到 windows 语言吗？
真正的 bash 即将到 windows 这不是
一个虚拟机，这不是交叉编译工具是本机 ubuntu
我们到那神奇的一个新的 windows 子系统在 windows 上运行的 linux 二进制程序
部分与规范提供这伟大的领事的经验
你将能够直接从 windows 应用商店里面的 bash 下载
访问本机文件系统 vt 一百支持 sh
和您收藏的所有命令行工具让我们潜入科技可以参考一下。
所以，在这里我有一个网站上夯运行边缘浏览器
是我们建造它红宝石网站托管在蔚蓝维也纳 linux vm
azure 和我可以我还建立了一个承载的 web 应用程序与它这样我
使用启动应用程序所有不得不做是采取伯爵创建它的名称和
提交到 windows 存储任何生产前我时在用户下载下载的应用程序
这里所以没有尚未到任何额外的但我想去做这件事来活着，
做得更好一些之前采取的能力是一个银行应用程序网站科技使用的能力
本机的相机和真的像期望所以我设备上获得伟大的相机体验
跃过这里吗？
以痛击。
所以，在这里你看看我做我可以看到我要搬过来我本地系统的 ls
我 c 驱动器整体性自动完成功能在这里。
不是我第一次使用
前去修改我 javascript 只是两个的部分我 javascript 归结，灯和使用
windows 功能然后需要更改后端我 ruby 代码。
当然我最喜欢的输入是 emax 如此。
要使用 emax 但是你可以使用所有他们是任何您的收藏夹
他们所有的调查都可以选择他们最喜欢的那个。
你在这里看到我，我在这里入住一个主意首先这样做的 javascript 是怎样确保我可以
我如果我在我只是检查应用程序运行的代码看看窗户是否的共享
那里的定义如果它是和享有所有的 windows api 如果不是，我在承载
浏览器加载项的权利以及此代码你可以在这里看到我我只是铸造
标准的 rt api 让访问得到
原产经历，因为他们是本机应用程序 api，
保存打电话实际上了别人，现在我要去 sh 向
我通过 linux 和 azure 那里。
尝试自己找我的密码。
所以，在这里。
我会让它再次使用 emax 修改此文件吗？
所以，你知道，像对所有这些
演示我扫描评论一些代码只是时间太长，其实去
修改它令人敬畏的罕见用它保存所有我需要做的 ruby 代码是重新启动，
所以我得到的最新版本的应用程序。
解决了流行在这里发射它你可能会注意到在这里它编辑
在我的用户界面的新菜单项没有所以我可以说在这里扫描检查
底片的本土经验，收到了这种检查在这里为乔治 ·
一千块钱，但我是真的不实际上可以拍张照片，因为它反弹，最后一次
很明显可以退出在这里和你知道，这样做
与 bash 来到 windows 带来
我们的开放源码到 windows 的命令行工具。
你觉得怎么样？
为你的萨摩亚。
网站。
所以，现在时候问有多少人在这里建立了
一个赢三十二个应用程序或点 net 应用程序中。
为权利假你的一部分
在我们 windows 家庭所以今天我 m 兴奋地宣布该单词的
现在添加桌面应用程序转换器四到寒冷
与此转换器点净动作游戏需要
现有的桌面应用程序和转换成百年什么
我们现在称之为现代桌面应用程序开发人员可以现在利用
现代应用程序和游戏的并将其提交到 windows 应用商店。
与此转换代码将继续运行
极少更改此外现代桌面应用程序
此外可以访问所有的通用 api 时
运行在 windows 上十让我们看到这个萨摩亚。
在这里我是微软我 m 运行需要的桌面应用程序转换器
现有的安装程序在这种情况下它是 msi，但它可以是一组的
x 你有任何安装程序，它将转换工作与圣人谁
最初有会计软件转换他们的圣人
两百年应用到现代的桌面应用程序可转换生产
前包，鼠尾草可以在应用程序提交到 windows 应用商店
就像任何其他普遍的应用，所以在这里要做什么是冷漠
农产品在这里是双击，现在我们已经添加了支持双击的顶部
史诗是使它易于安装和调试本地猜测小 delighter 右那里战斗
选择获取现场砖和充分融合实际上已经安装从存储区，所以你可以在这里看到
开始菜单我当现在有三十二个喷头阶段冬日到应用程序
访问生活瓷砖和显示一些销售数字可以点击到它和
启动应用程序最小化，你会看到它也能到
意大利面烤面包班戈解雇我告诉你这在 visual studio 中我不得不去
做到这一点，所以那里是一个单一的解决方案在这里吗
两个项目第一次是赢七 codess 是只是你冬天到代码的标准
这里不作任何修改为什么修改它没有给它会
只是过了然后加上这额外的项目，这是普遍的代码，虽然
所以圣人加载时现场砖
能够检查这个软件运行在 windows 十将加载 ll 和使用的额外功能
否则继续喜欢它，在这里你看到这个样板标准，
你知道，通知，活出普遍的 windows 代码只是直的瓷砖代码。
所以，我也很高兴来分享这鼠尾草
两百个将在今年夏天到 windows 应用商店来和
对于那些你水龙头继而安装屏蔽或该工具集
将使用 flexera 和 firegiant，所以直接产生现代应用程序软件包
你甚至不必使用转换器礼物更新你
说您的项目和他们得到前的两个应用程序，以及您的 msi 我们正在
它容易给开发人员带来超过 1600 万
当三十二被起诉到 windows 应用程序存储最后。
我们希望 windows 是你的家，不只是为开发应用程序的 windows，而是为了发展
当我谈到开发人员的所有设备的应用程序隐藏许多
我们你使用体系结构有一个共享共同的核心
你建立本地 ui，因为你们每个人都敦促平台，你的目标
在最后照亮了本机功能与特定于平台的 api 的东西
如相机通知和商务 csharp 开发商他们
仍然可以使用你 wb 对成长目标成长过种植基地的 windows 启动
十设备在现在树林 xamarin 你可以针对 ios
和 android 作为让我跳越过视觉工作室和给你看。
所以，在这里我们看着真正的微软健康应用程序的代码时候
到微软乐队的同伴 app 你们都有乐队在那里绝对令人敬畏。
所以，微软带用户有 windows android 和 ios
所以健康团队需要对他们都有一个应用程序的设备。
Udp 的应用程序，他们开始使用 xaml ui 的顶部
包含核心业务逻辑 csharp 库和
服务连接性因为医疗软件设计了这种方式很容易
使用 xamarin 来把它带到 ios 和安卓让我告诉你
这里项目所以这里的底部是一个的价格我有这
大部分的代码是在不同的平台之间的所有共享的代码
他有大量的代码，你真的是说这是实际健康应用格式
所示的代码和左侧私底下在这里很多你想要显示有时真正的代码吗？
注意到相当容易，和现在有的一句话项目达到
一个通用应用程序，他们开始与任何人为 ios 和安卓系统的一个负责人
好的事情是与 xamarin 你不只能调试
我们现在也有能力做内循环，循环的 windows 模拟器
发展为其 android 的头有 android 的模拟器你可以去运行和
windows 和后来以及另外 ios 开发商我们还
曾有一个远程的设计师，所以你呆在 visual studio 中的能力
你整个的时间爱呆在 visual studio 中在整个
时间在这里我到远程设计器
你调整如果他们 ui 在推特以及 ios。
windows 现在可以是你家中的开发应用程序的所有设备
现在在我走之前我想亲自感谢您对我们的开发人员
花时间来给我们反馈到部分，和我们一起
共同建设的极好平台
保持反馈到来，我们不能建立平台无需，
你知道，回到特里。
与此周年更新我们真的一直专注于制作 windows
十最好家里所有的你。
使您能够选择无论壳你
要当 powershell dos。
或更多即将推出。
使您能够拥抱新的设备功能，如
windows 允许 windows 油墨使您采取您现有的点
net 冬天到应用程序并将它们分发
通过 windows 存储和加强他们与
所有新设备的功能我们一直在谈论。
使您能够
建立新点 net 代码基地，把他们带跨平台，当然，如果
你正在为高性能精密笔记本电脑和
平板电脑做所有你对我们的发展有表面
有真的没有更好的时间是 windows 开发人员。
现在我们拥有此周年更新超越的经验
电脑让我们采取游戏你想要超越您的移动设备进
你的客厅你利用你有游戏领事
他们你一的 xbox 或全息透镜是
世界上第一个完全不受限制的全息计算机。
在过去的几年。
全息透镜已经从一场梦。
对一个原型。
现在今天我们能看到真正的客户用干什么它每一天。
请欢迎刘飞讨论游戏和
然后亚历克斯 kipman 将加入我们讨论全息计算。
更重要的是
体育六十八个文本是的第一步在堡垒迁移到 windows 的十位专营权
集中带来的什么赛车已向核在 pc 上提供最好的经验。
教学语言文本实际上是
批准的什么第一的方能做与欧洲 directx 十二点
通用的 windows 平台都能够驾驶它四 k 和 60 帧
第二我们已经过提供普遍的方面，是一个真正的高保真度
真实的应许，我们是到雷达代码一个商店仍然去的能力
泰勒的经验，这是最好的东西，你可以在 xbox 你能相处的最好的事情
个人电脑，但它意味着它有减少开发时间，我们真的
表面不只在代码中，我们成熟但也该工具
说我们要使用，这是要增长最快时间 moi 的事情
第一方是以确保每个人都在运行该平台是最好的他们可以
提供对移动游戏转发所有我们的约会，你要在 windows 上航运
倾向于 xbox。
通用的 windows 平台是伟大的游戏
开发人员和游戏玩家都要变得更加强大，作为一种方式提供的令人惊叹
在所有设备和 windows 生态系统的都经验。
大家早上好你好，我是菲尔 · 斯宾塞
自豪地代表，在这里我第一次生成会议
代表负责在微软游戏的人才和创新团队。
你听说过今天早上如何 windows 是最好的平台
开发商今天我们会花时间谈论 windows 的是
布莱德的最佳平台，为游戏开发商的大型社区的
通用的 windows 平台为开发人员提供的能力
右脚游戏和跨所有 windows 十设备从桌面部署
平板电脑和手机和 xbox 今天早上。
谢谢你今天早上我们将演示如何提供 windows 十
对于开发人员来说最高效和有效的平台
所有尺寸的因为 windows 并将继续是
在那里，任何人都可以建立一个开放开发生态系统
部署销售和服务他们在应用程序中的游戏？
开放视频我们要听到直接从我们的第一方工作室之一
十上带来的普遍 windows 平台帽子影响转
极限竞速赛车六先端到 windows 十和如何 uw
p 可以受益开发商和玩家一样吗？
通过通用 windows 平台我们的计划
它将运行在更好的交付的游戏
与更可预测的性能更强大的 windows 安装卸载
和服务通过一个现代应用平台的能力。
和更安全的用户通过一个受保护的运行时环境
和现代桌面应用程序任何存储上的分布
包括 windows 应用商店和通过任何发展这种部署机制。
我们最近推出了三大片中
windows 存储战争终极版的古墓丽影齿轮的崛起
和昨天刚杀手本能季节三。
而且，我盼望即将发射之际，量子休息到下个星期。
我们听到了来自 pc 游戏社区响亮而清晰的反馈我们
十工作，以确保 windows 有着丰富的比赛经验
我们将启用禁用 v 同步和添加支持的能力
g-同步和 freesync 在可能 directx 十二添加的支持新
今天工作三十二这两个窗口的多个 gpu 方案
可以-你洼游戏。
我们致力于确保我们达到或超过性能
全屏游戏，以及其他功能的期望
要求包括对覆盖改装和更多的支持。
我们也知道你们很多人有
三十二个游戏代码基地今天的胜利，我们想给你访问
轻松地打包你的游戏作为现代桌面应用程序的能力
通过桌面应用程序转换器让我们看看，看看这是如何工作。
所以，我最喜欢的一个游戏，我听到它是
最喜欢的我们的创始人是帝国时代所以
我们所做的就是我们去 ht 你可以看到了帝国时代追加
这是你会从蒸汽在今天是可用的软件包的开始菜单
实际上如果你看你会看到活的瓷砖打开，你会看到那些人数目
其实玩这游戏活现在和 steamworks 我们有五一千两百二十
三名球员，所以我们所做的就是我们从蒸汽拿包跑通过转换器，并把它
在现代的桌面应用程序上让我们启动它，看它如何运行你可以看到
它启动我们的初始屏幕。
支持踢。
坚持这是所以我们现在在年龄到运行只作为
将运行如果你买了它从蒸汽今天多人游戏是这里之一
要求我们听说从人民支持为多器官功能障碍，这如何工作的东西，你知道，
任何关于年龄太，你知道，和我们这里有国防部的蒸汽车间是名单
每到我能作的 mods 的发生任何这些适用的选择我
反对跑步时运行版本的游戏在这里和他们可以正常工作，但是我想去
其实引导游戏吗？
而且，只是显示使用证明是在这里。
你在那边的年龄做八 d 作为一个现代化的桌面运行
利用所有的功能，windows 的应用程序站启用
虽然我爱年龄瓜籽到我们想要挑战自己多一点，看看如何我们
平台支撑，所以我们做了一个实验在这只是
与我们的朋友在裁谈会暂红色我们花了巫师发生但为实验
作为今年二〇一五年 pc 游戏的很多人一个了不起的游戏它穿过
相同的转换器让我告诉你它是如何工作的在这里是找到开始菜单。
它的更大的游戏需要更长一点时间的负载。
那么是什么你会看到母语教学。
有它是作为一个现代的桌面应用程序运行全帧速率巫师吗？
这允许这些游戏
利用公共服务和科技两个 xbox
在 windows 中帐篷东西活的特定于平台的功能像平铺的支持
通知像你只是刚才在此演示和凯文的演示中看到我们
在所有有一致输入的支持与控制器与鼠标和键盘
我们的设备和 windows 存储或任何其他存储中的分布。
我们已经说过，从一开始我们想 xbox 的人是游戏的好地方
和也的好地方开发商的所有大小以便您可以创建新的游戏
和应用经验今天我
很高兴地宣布为开发人员提供的 xbox 开发模式
若要将其零售 xbox 一转换开发工具包的能力。
请欢迎轴骑自行车的人从我们的 xbox 平台团队显示我们如何
谢谢阿什莉我们正在建设一个真正通用的平台，您的应用程序运行无处不在的位置
包括 xbox 其中提供给应用程序开发人员带来巨大的商机
他们的经验，所以现在客厅里生活会向您展示如何谁都可带
零售 xbox 之一，把它变成开发工具包。
我在这边玩堡垒，但真的想要做是我的 app 灰照片，看看工作
你在分钟但首先我需要我的领事投入开发模式。
所以，我们到那边去
现在运行 dev 模式激活应用程序，我已经从商店下载。
这个应用程序允许您注册您的领事作为 deb 领事已经做使用我
同一科目中死中心在哪里我提交其他威斯康辛大学
这意味着，可以为开发模式与按一次按钮切换 p 应用程序。
一旦完成了 xbox 重新启动它将在开发模式下这意味着我可以
部署和调试我的应用程序现在归因时咱们过去到这里
看看在 pc 上运行在哪里我实际上写的 asch 照片与 pc。
所以，你可以看到如何移动和调整作为变化的大小 ui 元素
窗口，现在让我们看看如何我们可以将这个主题的应用程序部署到 xbox 之一
所以我会停止调试在 pc 上这里，我再换
本地计算机到远程计算机，这是我的 xbox 的 ip 地址。
而且，然后信号。
并且，因为我已与我可以做我 xbox 匹配 visual studio 远程部署就像
任何其他普遍的 windows 设备。
没错所以这是我的领事年我在一个我 xbox 上运行的应用程序，
这是我们都只调试在这里，但现在的确切相同的代码
它是关于领事你可以告诉，它被优化的起居室里。
好消息是工作的普遍 windows 平台做了大量繁重，
例如，控制器只是工作
所有的 xaml 控件已经过优化，工作与游戏坏就像你会
预计包括焦点导航并不只出现在 xbox。
作品以同样的方式和桌面，当你有一个控制器插入所有的事实
xaml 控件旨在触摸鼠标与控制器工作的伟大。
乐于助人的生活。
这也意味着，
你可以继续测试，当你没有你的 xbox 看在你回家的航班。
现在因为这是一个普遍的 windows 应用程序它也能访问相同
所以对语音识别和合成包括 api 的通用 api
我已经添加了一个有趣的功能，允许我向我的照片我可以简单地使用添加泡泡
语音识别器填补他们的 xbox 是
所以比打字更容易让我告诉你这个作品，现在的这张照片会有添加题注。
狮子对树皮。
我们去那里的繁荣。
所以，更容易比打字。
好吧，我想给你们看一件事这么增补
dev 模式激活应用程序显示较早前还有另一个应用程序
将自动加载的 dev 家呼吁你们领事，一旦你把它在开发模式下。
而且，当你运行它拥有你需要的一切是来自任何从帐户管理到开发人员
开发人员设置最重要的是曾经的我做我的应用程序工作
因为昼夜想回去玩极限竞速可以吧，
按许可开发人员模式并回到零售模式吗？
我应该提及 dev 模式预览将可从今天开始。
谢谢阿希礼。
我们致力于把每一个 xbox 一成开发工具包
是入爱好得到的承诺
这是一个承诺，使每个开发人员在这个星球上的，以达到
在一个开放的应用程序平台上最大可寻址的电视观众。
但是，使开发人员能够创建和部署 uw 关键应用程序和游戏在 xbox 之一是
我们将仅仅是个开始与即将到来的 windows 十周年更新
继续我们提请所有 windows 设备活 xbox 的进展
和 windows 十，数以百万计的玩家连接到 xbox 应用程序
在世界各地我们也将添加单个统一存储
跨设备给开发人员的新功能和消费者
新的支持将是一致的体验将包括功能
游戏开发者来预期和需要从 xbox 一成
windows 存储包括支持为束季节通过预订和
更我们也将会从宾馆到 xbox 一
柯塔娜将成为您的个人游戏助理将有助于帮你找到
新大新游戏挑战或帮助你的技巧和窍门。
和一些大多数要求的新特性基金会
背景音乐，也会与周年更新等功能。
将宣布新的周年更新功能之一的 xbox 和 windows 十在你
在 6 月的三个？
命运最后我想关闭与技术
这使开发人员可以跨一个 xbox 和 windows 自己的投资收益最大化
十 directx 十二允许开发人员
要解锁在 pc 中的图形硬件的全部潜力
xbox 一它是最强的有效的图形 api，我们已经过
运我们看到令人难以置信的行业通过 directx 十二事实上它已
在历史上任何 directx 版本快通过。
让我们看看什么，我们可以
交付时把星球谢谢最大地产商的手中。
早上好，每个人都哇什么惊人
时间是 windows 开发人员男人意识到从 xbox。
对全息图窗口和我们通用平台是
在这一未来正在创建一个未来
那是不可能在任何其他平台或设备集最后
年在这里建立我们问你分享我们的梦想，
全息明天，我们使三维的未来
全息内容到现实世界中加强了我们
体验感知我们普通范围之外的生活。
而且，今天是一天
在那里我们从梦见混合世界跳下。
把微软全息透镜成为
现实的完全 windows 支架和帮助。
谢谢。
和，来帮助我们庆祝这一时刻大都会帮我欢迎
在舞台上全息透镜是共同创造者工藤角田。
嘿，工藤。
世界涉水地宣布，我们感到非常自豪，今天
三月三十二十四十六微软全息透镜
第一次和仍然唯一不受限制的全息电脑
将启动航运我们的 windows 开发人员和企业合作伙伴
我们的旅程就从这里开始现在与
所有的你我们的创造者我们的梦想我们的窗户
开发人员。
应莫伊吗？
我已经等待这一刻很长时间。
而且，因为全息透镜是一种 windows 表态
设备所有我们的工具都是熟悉您的投资在威斯康辛大学
张将继续发扬，但有点帮助
有了灵感让我更新你对我们较早前推出的项目
今年被称为分享你的想法提交社区
我们可以生成所有的你的应用程序的想法投票
和我们建立了。
我们在只是短短的六周内建银河资源管理器
我们记载路上项目本周我们
完成这项工程，今天我们将宣布
该项目要在 windows 商店和所有的涨
代码将在网上提供通过 github 让我们快速了解一下。
用全息透镜开发工具包，走进世界我们要求社会你会想什么
我们来帮你建立后这么多五千多想法投票支持
银河资源管理器中我们已经侵入你的头脑风暴过程
原型设计和开发的全息透镜星系资源管理器是跳下来点
全息透镜用于开发，所以你实际上可以下载所有我们的源代码，看看如何我们公司
凝视的姿态声音空间声音和空间映射，然后使用，直接在
您自己的项目，我们想向您展示如何我们实际开发应用程序通过视频和博客
我们让的邮政-你走进我们的发展过程我们也带来了在共享你的想法
部队派遣国看看银河资源管理器中，给我们的反馈
从看起来像有如此多的可能性收集构建的应用程序，我想要推
在萨摩亚创建边界。
还有还有那么多多，您可以必须是应用程序，现在我们想要看到什么想法你
可今天，他们好像问过。
您可以使用它的源代码是灵感的典礼。
萨摩亚。
从个人开发者
客户来样沃尔沃欧特克和特林布尔。
成千上万的人已经
过去一年的经验全息透镜。
梦见全息经验
最终成为飞行员和最终
变得实际经验部署在生产中的变化
我们的工作的方式交流学习和游戏技术大厦为例
他们正在重新思考整个施工规划过程
从第一球通过突破性发展或
以日本航空在另一方面他们有视野全息计算
影响的每个领域
他们的训练和操作，现在这些都只是两个例子的公司
和所有的形状和大小在全组织
范围的行业的人士，正试用惊人通用
windows 应用程序创建专为混合现实
在我们新的全息景观，但飞行员。
概念验证最终会搬到去年的产量
在这里生成教授马克格里斯沃尔德在和我一起在舞台上。
在我们向您展示一个概念证明在哪里使用全息透镜来创新
在如何医学生学习。
在同一时间案件西部储备大学和克利夫兰
诊所的他们全新的医学学校建设破土动工
设施令人惊异的设施，
将使用全息透镜作为关键的一部分他们的课程现在过去两
几个月十二个月这样的概念验证已搬入生产和
今天我很荣幸能有医生帕梅拉 · 戴维斯
案例西方储备大学医学院临床医学专业成院长
我们的团队成员亨利和杰夫加入我们，告诉我们更多
关于教学医学全息透镜的欢迎仪式。
医生大卫莫伊。
早上好。
在案件西部储备我们的座右铭是想超越
可能。
今天我们和克利夫兰诊所正在建设
未来的健康教育校园。
在这栋楼内我们的学生将学习使用
最期待使用看教育节目全息透镜
去年我们展示了几件事，我们认为现在是关键的一部分
可能用全息透镜。
自 10 月份以来，我们已经有三个小团队
我们的想法变成现实的计算机程序员。
今天我们要去拿给你看我们的工作
我们全息解剖程序的示例
小时的我们已经创建现在解剖学的课程内容是所有关于
掌握复杂的系统，在身体和你可以看到从消化
系统在这里有很多部件在一个狭小的空间。
学生需要了解不仅如何这些部件组合在一起，但如何
他们在一起工作亨利你能告诉我们哪个机关在体内
是帮助消化，也使胰岛素
将胰腺是有点难以看到它后面的胃在这里
但值得庆幸的是与全息透镜是非常容易得到的东西的最佳视图。
现在是我们学生要充分把握较难的另一个领域是紧张
系统。
全息透镜可以使这更容易通过改进
我们超越单一的课堂的互动学习。
教授马克格里斯沃尔德可以教我们的解剖
脑即使他是在克利夫兰让我们告诉你这是如何工作。
你有标记？
你好 pam 我每个人都欢迎来到我们的新教室。
这是我们新的系统，让我教给学生，与你互动，即使我不在那里
在生成我会告诉你这种感觉真的很自然，我们三个可以看到每个
对方的谈话，使我们感受到连接，甚至虽然你只能看到我
头和手你了解我的身体语言这是
真正改变它意味着要在类标记让他们展示白色物质
跟踪这些大片像超级公路允许
旅行从大脑的一部分到另一个本示例的消息来自
真正的病人，从实验室的教授 mri 扫描
它是在案件西部储备大学卡梅伦麦金太尔
关键我们的学生知道如何这些结构涉及到另一个可以告诉你
我看过像这样的数据集十多年，永远不会理解
直到我看见他们让我们在全息透镜的三维结构说我们有个病人的大脑
正显示出这里与此红色区域嘿杰夫和亨利的肿瘤。
你能看到这种肿瘤与光蓝道但不是绿道的相交或
黄色的那个，这使我们能够预测对此肿瘤的影响
耐心的症状和他们手术后的结果吗？
这可能会影响枕叶回到这里。
这可能会损害病人的视力可能也会影响
事先叶在这里会影响他们的触感吗？
我们的学生更快学习事实像
更多的时间，他们在茶
和他们一同思考我们在教他们觉得像一名医生。
感谢马克今天加入我们。
再见大家。
正在不插电能够走动三维全息内容
会使我们的学生真正有优势的学生评论说十五分钟
全息透镜与会话可以保存他们几十个小时中
帽尸体实验室
当我们有短短的 4 年间，培养他们这是极有价值。
我们都很感谢微软给我们的机会
开发这项技术，我们迫不及待地想与其他人协作。
使用
全息透镜去思考，去看到超越的可能。
只是令人惊异的谢谢你这么多。
非常感谢。
现在是美国国家航空航天局
我们第一个伙伴，在他们取得了令人难以置信的进步
去年他们已经开发出几个应用程序
那已经部署在生产让我们快速了解一下。
美国国家航空航天局，兴奋地将混合现实技术应用到我们面临的挑战
在空间探索协作与微软建立
应用程序支持工程师负责设计装配航天器
行动上的国际空间站和科学家的工作现在正在使用我们的火星
到现场在特派团行动现场向强大的托尼卡车科学家和
工程师便携式点头，而是因为我们一直觉得它应该保持
只有在转让采取现场核心
惊呆了，惊讶的经验，让公众提出了傻瓜的威胁。
我们称这个新经验目标教学语言。
火星可以是一个寂寞的地方，所以我们创建了全息捕获一名宇航员
在好奇心流浪者队的成员在指导这个旅程这一点
游戏是永生英雄莫伊博佐的机会。
期待开放目的地火星在肯尼迪航天中心的游客复杂展览
和夏天我们迫不及待地想与世界分享这次旅程的二十六个团队
萨摩亚。
而且，这里是最好的部分。
谢谢你。
而且，使用我最喜欢的部分美国国家航空航天局带来目的地火星
您对生成会议以便所有的
我们的 windows 开发人员可以到世界上的第一人
查看火星从美国国家航空航天局科学家今天工作相同的角度。
全息透镜星今天航运。
标志着。
谢谢。
标志着我们的旅程与交互的另一大步
计算机
过多个人的方式我问的所有的你。
实际上加入我们，帮助我们创建。
这种新的现实，我们的合作伙伴已经完全
在过去的十二个月和进步是什么
短的壮观让我离开你今天用的快照
他们巨大的创造力，我希望能看到所有的你这周你在生成谢谢你。
它太棒，看看 windows 平台上的事情之一，
最高兴约是如何成为 windows
dev 框中的选择是否你正在写冬日到应用程序并将其转换
进入现代的桌面应用程序编写通用的 windows 应用程序 web
应用程序或甚至 linux 后台或
ios android 应用程序，您可以在 windows 上好吗他们和其
去看看那开发人员带来一个奇妙的爱建。
也是真的很兴奋，约我认为机会新的前沿。
Windows 同时表示所有的你作为开发人员无论是
写下一个笔应用是否它语音应用程序
它的计算机视觉所有这些新的领域，我认为是的全息图
一个绝佳的机会，在那里你可以了解很多他们在生成和我们真的很希望到
看到你在我们的商店的创作那又怎样
是现在开关齿轮，谈谈作为一个平台，这次谈话。
正如我说这是所有的交汇处
我们三个平台 azure 办公室三六五以及 windows 站。
事实上，它是
你知道，最好带一段轶事作为一个整体。
她知道与我有关共享是购物中心。
雅虎的八十岁住在中国，她已经尝试使用因为
奶酪影响计算机和她发现很难甚至
网络虽然是一个伟大的民主化的力量计算她发现
它难导航网站之间是不舒服的点击
长度移动电话和 app 革命 ob
进一步民主化的东西，但即使在那里会和找到了合适的应用
是困难的所以她从来没有得到周围使用它使用 sms 和
现在与微信她不能够不是八十岁
无缝只有所有人交谈，但
她也是能够与企业进行交互和
，这表明我们。
人类的语言。
我们想要我们的人类语言，正如我早些时候所说
更普遍的将其应用到所有的计算接口和
计算的相互作用和做到这一点，虽然你要注入。
计算机和计算我们周围意味着你的情报
要带来这些技术的机器和人工智能
学习，我们可以教电脑学习。
人类的语言有教他们的会话理解
广泛的范畴内的人的地方的东西。
关于您的首选项的情况下你自己的知识。
所以，他们真的可以帮助你与你的日常任务
和在工作中和其他地方的日常生活。
所以，当我们注入。
情报
到一切我认为它是非常重要的是要有原则的方针。
指导我们的设计以及如何我们建造东西的方式吗？
因此，在微软我们专注于在接地的方法我们
特派团授权人和世界各地的组织实现模型
这里的三个核心原则首先我们想要建立
智力，增强人的能力和
经验最终不要对人机
要用我们的机器每个男人
excel 非常不同的事物。
我们有创造力移情情感的事实。
和判断。
那可以然后混与快速的计算能力，因此对大量
数据和做模式识别快它是那汇集
我认为是会帮助我们推进我们的社会？
同时，亦要右转入意味着我们技术建立信任。
你一定要有内置保护隐私权的技术
东有的透明度你有安全以及法规遵从性。
最后。
所有的技术，我们建立更加包容和尊重
我们需要建立技术，以便更多的人可以使用技术。
而且，我们希望
打造这种技术，它获取最好的人类不是最坏。
这已经指导我们，因为我们建立 Skype 翻译。
有会话的认识，为我们打造出有从宾馆
更多的专业知识作为我们生成全息透镜有环境的了解。
重复使用这种方法，当我们搞错了其实只是上个星期当我们
发起了我们这是在美国社会 bot 的孵化泰
我们很快意识到，它没有达到这个标记。
所以，我们又回到制图板。
为什么我们继续孵育 xiaoice 和意大利船级社在
中国和日本，了解为什么是它有社会的机器人会以不同的方式工作？
而且，这是如何我们想取得的进展，这种方法总是要
前面--中心给我们。
当我们谈到对话作为一个平台
反应堆有的浴场人吗？
我们希望能够和其他最自然的交谈
人。
事实上，我们想充实我们
对话和 Skype 翻译是一个出色的例子，因为我能
谈到不同的语言和真的有自动翻译
我们也有的存在你看到在全息
演示如何你可以有远程存在。
这些都为我们提升人类的谈话的所有方式。
但我们想要同我们的人类对话和适用于一切
而且，这是这些其他行动者进来个人数字的地方
你知道你对世界的助理就在你身边
在您的设备帮助你你完成每天的任务。
机器人就像你交谈的新应用程序
你不是真的想为多个应用程序。
页和页网站或应用程序，但你只是能
调用任何应用程序作为 bot 右内会话的画布上。
所以，这是我们设想人民对人民的谈话的丰富世界
人们对你个人数字助理到人机器人和
甚至个人数字助理呼吁以您的名义的机器人。
这就是世界，你会想要在几年来看看。
因此，您可以使用此平台概念。
在人类的语言吗？
新的 ui 层吗？
机器人就像新的应用程序。
而且，数字助理元的应用程序，为如新的浏览器。
情报注入你们的互动
这是我们有丰富的平台。
所以，让我们开始。
通过谈论柯塔娜。
We introduced cortana two years ago and
ever since then it's becoming smarter every day.
Because of its ability to know you.
To know about your organization to know about the world
and reason about all of this on a continuous basis.
It's built natively into windows.
But, it's not limited to windows
it's going to be available on all your devices
whether ios android across all of your applications.
Because if it's going to be a useful personal digital assistant it has to be about
new not a single device and that's really
how we are building out cortana.
And, we're also making it such that the expertise of cortana is
extensible it's truly unbounded in that way so the opportunity
for developers to addicts their expertise the expertise that they have
in their applications this services into cortana
so that can further drive engagement for their applications
and services that developer opportunity is something that we want to talk about so to show
you how this unbounded personal digital assistant works across
all of your devices and creates this ability for developers to
extended with your expertise please help me welcome markets ash from the cortana team.
Good morning everyone it's great to be here at build to get a chance to give you an early preview of
our future plans first I want to talk about a new experience the anniversary update
we want windows to be the best place to have a voice conversation with cortana, cortana
is answering one million voice questions per day we have almost a thousand applications that
integrate with cortana voice commands and today there's a new cortana app store collection
available so customers can check out some great examples we want to go even further and
make a voice conversation with cortana as easy as a voice conversation with a human.
So, I've got this beautiful all-in-one with a nice big-screen you can see at the top left
corner cortana is ready for me to have a conversation I go sausalito tonight I don't know where that
is I don't know-how long it's going to take cortana can help me event hey cortana.
How long would take to get to sausalito?
It will take twenty-seven minutes to drive to sausalito it's about twelve miles
away all the things you expect to work in this experience on the lock screen I can play my
music I can set alarm and this also gives a much bigger stage to let cortana
is personality shine through.
Hey, cortana will tell me a science joke.
Sodium, sodium, sodium, sodium, sodium, sodium, sodium, sodium batman.
Vanna on nana old school batman, batman you guys with me.
This experience is going to be shipping in
the anniversary update it's also going to be available in thirteen countries.
Cortana is going to be here all week and the expo fair please go checker out but now I want to show you how
she helps me get stuff done here's an early preview of some new experiences that will release the coming months.
Notice that cortana is coming to outlook and
scheduled some appointments for me it's the blue with the circle.
The idea there is cortana is now in outlook and
she looking at my email and my calendar with my permission and
helping me get things done stay on top of things a good example this week I was exchanging a bunch of
email with our microsoft travel service trying to figure out the best time to get home on friday
cortana is able to understand that conversation about me doing anything adding
create appointment she automatically put all that flight information my counter to make it really easy for me to track.
She applies the same conversational intelligence to help me stay on top of commitments
in email I get a ton of email which makes it easy for me to forget things I said
I would do so here cortana is flagged something I said
semi manager today I was actually going to get ahead of this on the plane but the siren song of
that flight infotainment system gap me again no problem cortana is there and she
knows the last time I made an update she knows where the document as I can ask a good take care of this warming.
Send chuck the powerpoint that are worked on last night.
Sure, thing I found this powerpoint document is this it.
I go ahead and get that sent.
Since cortana is not bound to specific device thank you thank you.
Now since cortana is not bound to a specific device she helps me keep track of notifications that are
happening right here my android phone while I'm doing work on my pc.
So, here I've got a notification a text message that came in from my friend ben he's here in the bay area
what's michigan together go blue and we were talking about
get-together after the keynote any michigan grads out there we go for.
I can go ahead and respond right here for my pc.
Cortana knows that I'm talking about meeting with ben she offers to add
this to my calendar.
And, then she tells me got a couple of other things there can I help you movies.
But, see then are some work-related stuff I choose ben and what she did
there is appointments from noon on wednesday
automatically shift to the appointment the free block of time I have there on thursday?
Now since that meeting with ben is over lunch you can see here the cortana is brought
in some proactive actions that she thinks can help me cortana has a team of experts
that she relies on this idea that cortana doesn't need to know everything she can go and ask experts
for health experts are all of you developers that are creating these amazing apps and services that can integrate
right into cortana so the cases this meetings over lunch I might want to book a table
we might not have time so I might need to bring in some food or she can offer some helpful
suggestions about things to do here you can see a bunch of options city food tour sounds great
here some information about that notice the option to buy tickets.
Extensibility also means help me get that action done here create a very simple sample application
city food tour notice cortana is passed in some context for me there are two of us in the meeting
invite here some other information I can confirm my order now I've got tickets purchased.
This same experience also works for business applications so the next time I go to cortana
she's queuing up another thing she thinks I might want to work on in this case I took a taxi
last night and cortana found out there was a receipt my email and she's
offered to help me put that into my expense report we use the microsoft expense
application internally to track this kind of thing when I click on that notice that all of the
information and details map receipt are put into that application.
And, I go ahead and add choose to save that.
Since cortana is not bound to a particular device I can finish all these tasks here
on my android phone.
So, when I go ahead launch cortana?
You can see that my meeting with ben is here and I got the tickets to the food city
tours the microsoft expense application here I go ahead and choose to submit that
and it's all taken care of since the phone as my most personal device
its with me all the time cortana can augment me in very interesting ways so I
have a five-year-old son and I started this tradition two years ago when I
brought him home a toy from a business trip.
Now every time daddy goes in a business trip little man thinks
is birthday and daddy better deliver and bring home yet another toy I
don't remember the name of the toy store that I went to last year was here but it
had great transformers and things that he wants so since cortana is with me she can help enhance my memory.
What toy store did I go to last year at build?
You can see she finds the correct toy store again she brings in helpful proactive actions.
Now let me show you how easy it is to create these actions.
Here on the developer portal today we're announcing an invite-based preview
for proactive actions and here's the portal that you can use to connect your apps and websites to cortana.
I want
to share two examples of partners that are already integrated glimpse and just the.
Glimpse provides an easy way to safely share your location with some and real-time
data great idea for improving the arm running late experience beatings.
Instead of fumbling around trying to figure out how to send a text message and figure out what am I going to
get there and I really going to get there at the time I think I can just send a glimpse which gives
all the attendees real-time tracking of me with a map and tells me my expected eta.
Just eat is a leading food delivery service based uk and they're very excited about scenarios like helping you
order dinner when you're working late let me show you how easy it was for just eat to configure the portal
only a few steps the first thing you do is you go and add insights,
insights control when cortana surfaces your action.
That's this column right here this column is the contextual info this is the information that you want
your app to request from customers so that just eat example just eat would like to know
my cuisine preferences because they can do a much better job of give-me helpful suggestions if they knew that I love sushi.
Customers are always in control of data that cortana shares so she's always going
to ask permission before any data sent applications and services.
Here the deep links that you create open your app these deep links are
not restricted to a particular device a platform we support windows applications we
support android applications ios applications are coming in the future and we also support websites.
And, then finally some metadata that you ads that shows how the experience shows up
in the cortana ui along with an icon.
So, here you can see a sample appointment and both glimpse and just eat
are here as actions it only take took just
eat fifteen minutes to get their app registered to work in this experience.
We're looking forward to seeing all the great ideas you have for integrating with cortana please request
an invites the cortana developer preview and I hope to see you at the cortana sessions thank you.
Thanks mark is that gives you a glimpse
of how cortana is a truly unbounded personal assistant that's always
with you and for developers it represents a new opportunity for
you for you to be able to take the
expertise that you have in your applications the intelligence that you have in your
services and then register them as extensions and insights and action.
So, we want to now move to another
canvas another set of tools where conversations are taking place these
are our communications tools there are a wide variety of their in fact we
envision a world where there are going to be in more and more communications
tools because that's one of the most innate things that we as people do.
And, we want all of these conversational
tools to become rich canvases for computation.
In our case we have outlook and skype.
And, we want to ton bs into these rich conversational canvases
skype has over three hundred
million connected users each month every day there
is over three billion minutes of.
Voice calls happening on skype so
it's a tremendous amount of activity so now
imagine if we can open up skype.
Not only to have all the rich people-to-people
conversations things that we are doing with skype translate or
skype on the hololens what if we can now.
Bring in.
Your personal digital assistant right to your conversational
canvas what if we brought the world a bots.
The new applications to be able to do anything.
Like hire cab.
Book a ticket anything that you may want to do that you've done historically with
applications and websites now with bots right from within skype.
We don't even stop there.
You want to add richness
to these bots so it's not just text bots.
We want to have animation you want to have videos and we also want
to have holograms and to show you this rich world of conversational
canvases starting with skype I want to invite up on stage lilian from the skype the lilian.
Right hello everyone
I'm super excited to be here with you today I get the pleasure of showing
you our vision for how we see intelligence integrated into one of the
most popular ways that people communicate today skype.
Estate that, you know, and,
love is going to be smarter more helpful and entertaining.
We're moving into a world where you will soon be able to plan trips shop.
Even talk to intelligent bots all from within your skype chat.
I'm going to show you a demo of this next generation of skype scented scape will work
on ios android mac web you name it and I m going to show it to you on my windows phone.
So, here I see that I have one missed notification let's see that's from.
And, odds from gurdeep for those of you that don't know
greedy start corporate vice president for skates I canning are this as so
let's go into it and you see I have a visual video mail from somebody I'm going to play it.
Hey, I just learned you with
us keynote codess again this year congratulations attacks everything universe skype.
That is amazing I am a huge fan of code osman a send him a quick thank you.
So, right away as you're seeing here
there are some new things in this next generation of skype you see this visual video mail so
we have a video message with the transcript right below this is one of the examples where
we taking intelligence from things like skype translator and bringing them directly into everyday features
like video messages and narrative is telling me the team has sent me a little something
so that's really nice I'll send him a quick little happy emoticon so in this next generation of
said the other thing that you'll notice in the canvas is my personal assistant cortana
is always there in the upper right-hand corner cortana is there if I want to talk
to her one-on-one or in a group or even as you can see here she subtly
improving my messages by highlighting key points in my text like codess.
So, I can tap on codess you see this rich card powered by bing that showing us
set code is a real organization that microsoft
sponsors to really promote women in technology which is something that I'm very passionate about.
So, now you see cortana is actually sending me a private message I'm going to tap that and I
go into the one-on-one conversation I have with cortana so she's telling me the
custom cakes bot would like to know my location for delivery and yes I'll share it.
And, what I like to track delivery also yes I'll share it so right away what you're seeing here is that?
The agent cortana
is actually brokering the conversation with the third-party bot the custom cakes bot
now I see this rich card that is showing me that the cupcake is on its way and that
it will be here within a few minutes all of this is happening within my skype chats.
This is just one example of the many ways that you're going to
start seeing businesses using the our of skype and cortana to interact with their customers.
Now since I'm already talking to cortana and
I've committed to doing this keynote I'm going-to go ahead and try to plan the rest of my trip.
Please block my calendar for codess from april ten through april twelfth.
These other used push talk because I didn't feel like typing.
And, reilly everything your notice here is that cortana
actually has context for my previous chat with gurdeep so even though I just told that the
date it actually knows the location and, you know, that its from the conversation with gurdeep.
Now cortana is proactively thinking about the next steps in coordinating my trip so
she's actually suggesting that I connect with the westin bot anybody that knows me knows I normally stay at
a westin bot and I'm so you see here now is cortana has actually
introduced the westin bot into the conversation but not only has
he done that she has given the westin bot
context so I don't have to repeat myself the westin bot knows this is for dublin and
its for those particular dates all of this saves me a lot of time and effort.
Now there are suggested rooms I'm going to choose the normal room.
Confirmation and just like that into simple steps I was able to
block my calendar and also book my hotel room.
Now there's nothing else the westin bot can do for me so I m going to say no thank you.
And, now because cortana has all my relevant details the westin bot can actually leave the
conversation.
Now we're seeing a third aspect of cortana she knows my
connections she knows who I communicate with
so here you're seeing her actually suggest that when I go on this trip to dublin that I communicate with
my friend jani and I see this card I could call her directly from here
are video call her but I don't know what time it is so I'm going to choose to message her clicking that
takes me to the conversation I have with jani the other thing you'll notice is that cortana because she has
context about why I m pinging jani she's prepopulated the text
with context around when I'm going to dublin and basically why I want to talk to her.
And, fantastic jani is available and she's even going to show me around tab.
So, this is just a glimpse into how skype and cortana
powered by bing can make our conversations more productive informed and fine.
Now as you now real-time video is a big part of how skype is used today
I just showed you intelligence applied to messaging conversations and I now have the
pleasure of announcing we will also be bringing intelligence into real-time video.
Skype video baths will reinvent the way that friends family
and businesses get together for the first-time we will enable a very personalized
experience for you to connect with your favorite character business or
And, the best part is that starting today
developers will have access to our first ever skype bot sdk.
And, as you can see there you can also sign up to one of our global hackathons we're starting with the first one in
may which is happening here down in silicon valley and you'll be able
to seamlessly integrate into chats like I showed you or even
invent totally new audio and video experiences for an audience of millions.
to make this even sweeter for developers as of today skype consumers will
have access to bots in our latest windows ios and android apps.
But, this is just the beginning with hololens becoming available we
are also bringing intelligence into your virtual conversations
with skype for hololens please roll video.
Now the new seen what these rich conversational canvases as well
as personal digital assistants can do for you.
developers we think that this represents a huge opportunity for you
to write new types of applications we want
to empower all developers to do this new work that
means we want every developer to build.
Experts for cortana.
We want every developer to be able to build.
Bots as the new applications for every business
and every service we want all developers to be able
to infuse intelligence into their applications.
to really make this possible we think of a new run-time.
Which is this intelligence run time?
That's all coming together as part of cortana intelligence suite.
The runs on azure.
That's going to have a rich bot
framework a bot framework that will allow you to build.
Rich dialogue capability into your application into your bot.
A bot framework that will allow you not just to build bots for any one
canvas
we don't envision such a world we envision a world of many conversational canvas.
So, you will be able to take the bot framework and in fact integrate with all of
slack skype line outlook all of the canvases.
We also want to give you a set of micro
services these cognitive services so that you can have language understanding
speech understanding computer vision built into your applications and
also rich machine learning capability because we think
of this intelligence run time and cortana intelligence
suite is going to be core just like how the dot net run times were.
To all the applications that you're going to build going forward.
And, to give you a glimpse of this world and what cortana intelligence suite
can enable warning white up onstage my colleague dan lili as well
as cornelia to give you a sense for what development looks like with these new set of tools
and micro services dan first new thanks satya?
In today's demos of windows cortana and skype we've shown you how
microsoft is creating new conversational experiences if
you're developer or business professional you may want to add
bots and conversations your own products and we want to share our services and open
source our tools so you can use them to build your own great bots.
So, today I m so excited to introduce a brand-new
platform for creating intelligent and connected bots the microsoft bot framework.
What are you're building a simple tick-tack-toe bot creating a productivity bot to make your business smarter
or faster or adding conversation to an existing brand like you saw with the westin bot the
microsoft bot framework has everything you need to get your bot stocking?
Let me give you an introduction.
If you've already got a bot the microsoft bot framework can seamlessly connect that bots
as users on skype slack telegram sms email and more.
Don't have a bot
our open source bot builder sdk available on github has everything you need to give your
node dot js or csharp based bot great dialoging conversation skills
and also makes it easy to integrate natural language processing and machine learning services coming
soon our bot directory will contain many fantastic bots written using the bot framework
including the build bot which is available to give you information about the build event like session
information nearby restaurants and more but
I'm a developer and I'm really excited to show you how easy it is to write code using the microsoft
bot framework to show you what it's like I put together a simple bot that orders me pizza from
domino's this is going to be great you're going to get to see some code and I get order myself lunch?
Here's the source code for my bot when a user sends my
bottom message the bot framework calls into this method right here and if user said
slashed order we drop into this block of code were first I put together my pizza
medium hand-tossed with spinach and mushrooms then I put that pizza into an order of
specified the delivery address and the credit card that I found.
That's a satya assures me use buying and then I place the order to
dominoes secure rest api now since I'm dealing with a credit card I don't
want don't transmit that and plain-text so I want to make sure
that's commit sent securely over secure channel
tryout our bot I'm going to show you my bots webpage in our bot directory.
Now it can be really hard to try out new bots so as part of the bot framework
we've included a reusable and secure will chat control that developers can
put in their own webpages so customers can talk directly with their bots.
Straight out of say hi to my bot and a respond if I
says such order will take just a second and there we go my orders on its way.
This is great for simple bots but interesting bots need real dialogue
and language skills that they can hold a real conversation I want my bot to be able to
excepted an order from a real customer where they can specify the size of their pizza the
toppings and more and you heard such talk about trustworthiness it's important for
robot to get the users permission before actually sends the order on its way to dominoes now this is
were a bot builder sdk really shines our bot builder sdk is available in node dot
js and csharp but I'm writing in csharp so I'll show you that.
Use our bot builder sdk I'm just going to remove the existing simple bot code
that I've got an ad in a couple of lines here.
And, then up at the top of configured the bot builder
sdk so, the my bot talks the way I want to I've added welcome message a
confirmation prompt and then actually added in the code place the order
the bot builder sdk does all the work of walking my user through filling in my
up the object that represents my pizza which are defined as a
plain csharp object with a few annotations now next we're going to actually connect my
bot to users so I'm going to go to my bots dashboard in the developed
in our developer portal in the bot framework a you can see here it's
easy to connect my bot up to services like skype slack telegram
and others we bought the bot framework to be an open platform so we include many third-party
services including pervasive services like sms which are accessible worldwide
and available even on inexpensive devices like this fourteen dollar mobile phone.
Now we're really excited to introduce the bot framework or even more excited to see the kinds of things
you write using it we have a session coming up immediately after the keynote at
eleven thirty were walk you through the process of building a conversational bot from zero to sixty
using the bot framework hope to see there are up next I like to introduce lili tang
is going to give you a sneak peek at some upcoming intelligent tools coming to the bot framework in the future.
So, as dan said I'm going to give you a sneak
peek at some tools we the experimenting with to help you build your bot sprayed.
All right so here I have
my chat control and I can type in please send me a large pepperoni pizza.
And, you can see that my bot understands the size and toppings
ask me to clarify what kind of crust I want.
Now in order to do this your bot needs to understand natural
language so as you begin before you have real users using your bot
the before you have real user response data we
provided some simple tools to help you build your natural language rules let's take a look.
All right so these are the rules behind my bot
brain just like dan showed you except we providing you why
do make them a little bit easier to read so if you look at the first rule it
matches responses such as deliver me some quantity of
some size pizza a with some kind of topping that's pretty cool right.
So, I can just click into the deliver blurb to understand it more and here you
can see that not only the word deliver triggers the verb but also order and
by so that's pretty cool too.
But, what if people use other words?
Because we mine the web and understand language things like verb
tense translation into other language common misspellings we can help
you by providing you some suggestions for synonyms.
All you need to do is click.
Select once you once.
And, you expanded dictionary really easy.
What else is great is if I have other bots like the cupcake bot that lilian
showed you earlier I can share these dictionaries across my various bots?
Now rules are great and critical for getting started but as you
start getting more and more users and more and more response data rules can
be very complex to manage and this is where we provide you with another tool.
Here we use machine learning
and deep learning to create your conversation model.
So, building upon what I just showed you we automatically add
your semantic dictionary and your rules we also make it really easy for you to upload
additional training data to get started now we know.
That people can be very unpredictable as they user bots.
So, here you can see a
user has said can you deliver three large pepperoni pizzas to my crib.
So, you're laughing so, you know, and, I know that my crib is slang for
house but the system doesn't know that so it's really easy for me if I
think it's appropriate to tag it as a location and
save so it's that easy to help teach your bot and help
become smarter and you don't need to be a data science expert in
fact you don't even really need to know how to code to help your bot improve.
So, that's pretty cool right.
All right so finally we
know intelligent systems have their limitations so here I take send me
a large pepperoni pizza a to moscone a that too.
Eric and here my body's telling me I don't understand.
And, what it can do for tasks that are rare complex?
Or just that it doesn't understand it can automatically escalate
to a person and this is something that we think is a great example of
what satya mentioned earlier to combine what people do
best with the intelligent system so let's take a look at what the worker might see.
All right so here as I'm working
the system in real time is automatically suggesting me responses and you can
see those responses below my text entry in the chat window.
And, then on the side the system
is automatically pre-filling my order form based on what it knows.
Now I can see here the system has incorrectly
classified moscone is a person so all I need to do it again is click.
Correct the annotation and save it.
The system prompts me to clarify that its moscone
center and again my suggested response is update I can just click
and enter to have to facilitate my interaction with my customer.
So, this is exciting because while working I can
continue to teach my bot without needing to know
natural language machine learning deep learning or even coding.
All of my input can make the system more intelligent and
the intelligent system can help me get my work done more effectively
that's it for my sneak peek we know we have a lot to learn.
As we continue to experiment and make we will make these tools more broadly available.
And, of course as you've already heard you can get started today with both
the bot framework that dan showed you earlier to build and connect your bot
to places people connect
skype bot tools and also cornelia is up next to show you the
new cognitive services which will help make your tools more intelligent thank you.
Thank you lili.
Ria hello everybody in a
year ago we introduced the first portfolio of intelligent services
from microsoft we had five apis for you to go use
and add intelligence to your apps.
Well, today I want to introduce you to microsoft dot com slash cognitive
our new portfolio of intelligent services and we have twenty-two
apis for you to get started with for free today.
We have apis we have apis
across vision from image to video understanding speech.
Language understanding apis.
Knowledge apis.
And, of course search apis through bing
twenty-two apis for you to get started with this is years
of machine learning and ai research from microsoft ready for you to use
at your fingertips now you can just samoa.
You can just imagine all the cool stuff you can build with these apis and to showcase what's
possible I'm going to show you a handful of demos the first
I'll show you is a quick app we put together all I need to do in
this app is either take a photo or upload some image url logistic
this desk here and use that it calls into the new vision apis and
what that is able to do is able to recognize objects in the image?
There are thousands of objects we can recognize and we also give you a confidence score if
the confidence is low, you know, we're not quite sure if for seeing what we say we're seeing if the
confidence is high you can probably take it for real.
Now it's cool we have object recognition we can take it a step further and role show you
in my next demo we can take it a step further by not just recognizing objects but also figuring
out the relationships behind them and then using natural language to create
a coherent description of what you're seeing in the image.
This is caption bot that ai and you them aware side we're going to allow you to
play with today I went in earlier picked up a couple of random images
off of bing and now let's see what our little caption bot signal to say
its thinks it's a herd of cattle standing on a dry grass field I love the fact
that it gives the vocabulary right that doesn't say group of cattle or group of animals no it's a
herd of cattle and it also sees that it's a dry grass field.
This is the mona lisa as most of you here now let's see what.
Our little caption bot can do.
All right so trips of its as I'm not really confident but I think if we have a heart
of the vinci sitting in front of the mirror and he seems neutral faced.
This goes to show you our bot wasn't taught any art so then it doesn't
recognize the masters of the renaissance of their masterpieces we haven't
shown it any of that data we've only shown it landscapes and gatherings and,
you know, your average day-to-day life to learn from.
And, I showed you this example to show just how important data is when you are
trying to take advantage of these machine learning a services an apis and
we're working on allowing you to bring your own data to these algorithms
and customize them for your needs.
Which frankly into my third demo?
This demo is a quick little app that we put together to show you a service we call
Custom recognition intelligent service it allows you to bring any audio
files and customize our speech-to-text technology that's already shipped in
products like cortana and bing so if your scenario
calls for audio that has a lot of background noise think of,
you know, a busy drive-through and you're trying to understand what you're customers ordering or think, you
know, you're trying to understand what people with heavy romanian accents like me are trying to say
well you bring those files and you're able to train the speech-to-text algorithms
to have higher precision for your scenarios what I'm showing you here is an example that we
trained with child speech and I hope the audio is hooked up because it's important to realize
just how bad the audio can be here and the difference between speech regular speech-to-text versus
cris left side shows you regular speech-to-text right side is
cris and now let's see what our system is able to recognize.
Chance like large bash.
They use case badge collects star.
We had some kids here read a book about giants and you can clearly see that cris gets
kids not talking about dancing is talking about giants and the fact that they love large bags.
No.
Thank you.
Now these demos are all fun I'm going to finish up by showing showing you a real
customer scenario witti globe is a
startup and they do real-time twitter analysis
monitoring they try to create a twitter analysis for anything from
brands to politics and I went in earlier and use the
products the dashboard that they offer their customers to actually create a dashboard for
the current presidential elections you can see them move
the entire election and this and this little blurb here the cool thing of a visual with that
it doesn't just give you these mood indicators it also offers extra of our context
like the gender of the people who tweet or their age ranges and,
creating these gender and age range indicators they actually use the vision apis
from cognitive services they use the vision apis to look at the profile image and add extra
precision to the age or the gender identification are they further
use cognitive services also filter out any kind of tweets or content
that are just irrelevant to the dashboards they are trying to create.
Now just like vidigrove who is one of the partners who has started testing our apis early on
you can go to microsoft dot com slash cognitive
today and get started for free we can't wait to see the
stuff you build with these cool apis thank you.
Thank you so much cornelia so hopefully you get
feel for the richness of these intelligent services that you can
And, now it is up to each of
faucets developers to imagine
what's possible imagine what boeing can do to
the business applications in the aerospace industry what case western
reserve can do to medical education what nasa can do
for space exploration what a fast-food restaurant can do
for order-taking through a drive-through using cris.
What a new saw organization can do to be able to interpret all
tax all images all videos on a social media stream in real time?
And, one developer
truly inspired me this last year very close to home for us at
microsoft I want to see what he dreamt of roll the video.
I'm saqib shaikh spiced
site when I was seven shortly after that I went to a school for the blind and that's way
who is continues to be talking computers and that radio open up a whole new world of ching.
Joined microsoft ten years ago as a software engineer by
love-making things which improve people's lives and one of the
things are always dreamt of since I was a university was this idea of something
back and tell you attending my but what's going on around.
I think it's a man jumping in the air doing a trick on a skateboard.
I teamed up with like-minded today is to make about which that today to and what is
around you states-based on top of the microsoft intelligence apis which
makes it so much easier to make this kind of thing the app runs on smartphones but also the on the pivot
head smartglasses when you're talking to a
bigger group tugs you can token there's no response and you think
is everyone listening greatly well or are they half-asleep and he never?
I see to faces forty-year-old man with the beard looking surprised
twenty-year-old woman looking happy the app can describe the general
age and gender of the people around me and what the relations off which is incredible?
One of things that's most useful bad the app is the ability to
read our text moi.
Could use the app on my side to take a picture of the
many and is going to guide me on how to take the correct photo
move camera to the bottom right away from the document and they will recognize the text redmi
the having ic appetizers salad ponies pizzas
pastas and years ago this was science-fiction I never thought it would be something that you
can actually do artificial intelligence days improving had to have a
faster right I'm really excited see where we can take moi?
As and today is always standing on the shoulders of giants building on top of
what went before in this case we've taken years of research from microsoft research to pull this
off I think it's a young girl throwing in orange frisbee in the dark for me it's
about taking that far-off dream and building one-step-at-a-time I think this is just the beginning.
Well-meaning it copter privilege.
To have a chance to share the stage with soggy.
And, you know, saqib took his passion his
empathy.
And, is going to change the world?
And, to me that's what build is all about he's here in
fact at build to network inspire other developers
learn himself on how to take is applications and make them better
but more importantly he's also here to teach she's got a couple
of your sessions that he's going to do as well and to me that's what makes
these developer conferences magical it is about being able to take our
passions our empathy and go after the opportunities that
we see go after the dreams that we have and what's a key was done has been
a real inspiration for me and we as developers have this tremendous opportunity
in a tremendous responsibility because not only do we get to dream
of the future we get to build the future I can wait to see
what you dream up and what you build thank you so very much have a fantastic build
faithfully?